新闻发布会
周五 上午 11点
道琼斯指数
迈克! 迈克! 迈克!
Mike! Mike! Mike!
听说有些银行要求联邦援助救市
I'm hearing that some banks may be requiring a federal bailout.
援助是不可能的
Bailouts are not on the table.
不过也许有些银行会需要大量资金输入
It is possible some banks may require massive capital infusions.
这不就是援助的意思吗
That's the literal definition of bailing something out.
不会进行援助的 我已经说清楚了
There will be no bailouts. I was clear on this point.
说的很清楚了
Very clear on this.
经济形势应对小组
周五 上午 11:10
道琼斯指数
那么下面
So, next up on the hit parade,
我们该决定援助哪些银行了
we get to decide which banks to bail out.
我希望联储局在哪藏着个
Well, I hope to fiscal fuck
装了几万亿美元的床垫子
the fed has a trillion dollars stuffed in a mattress somewhere.
有三家银行极需
There are three banks in danger that are gonna need
在周末输入大量资金
massive infusions of cash over the weekend.
实际上 我们最多只可以援助两家银行
Essentially, we can only afford to bail out two.
那如果我们什么都不做呢?
And if we do nothing?
那周一取钱就只能取出土了
Go to the ATM Monday and dust will come out.
我们不能凭政治因素来做决定
This is not a decision we can make based on politics.
- 不 当然不是 - 可是我们必须挽救简第斯资本集团
- No, definitely not. - But we've got to save Janders Capital
- 他们驻扎在伊利诺斯 - 选举需要伊利诺斯
- because they're based in Illinois. - We need Illinois.
那确定一个了 还有一个是选鲍尔斯丁-博尔翰银行还是EM韦瑞特?
That's one. Paulsten-Berheim or EM Wheelright?
EM韦瑞特是查理·贝尔德开的银行
Well, Wheelright is Charlie Baird's bank.
所以...
So...
我选EM韦瑞特
My pick is EM Wheelright.
你知道么 汤姆? 我觉得...
You know what, Tom? I think...
对 就这个意思
oh, yes. What he just said.
请不必要的人
Um, could everyone who doesn't
暂时离开一下好吗?
absolutely have to be here please leave the room?
感谢
Thank you.
- 女士 你千万不能援助查理·贝尔德的银行 - 为什么不能?
- Ma'am, you cannot bail out Charlie Baird's bank. - Why not?
因为看起来你关心你男朋友
Cause that's gonna look like you care more about your boyfriend
胜过关心经济 人民
than you do the economy, normal people,
或者其他总统应该关心的东西
and everything else you're supposed to care about.
- 比如艾滋 - 多谢你了 自闭症肯特
- AIDS for example. - Thanks, Kent's autism.
听着 我和查理·贝尔德之间已经没有私怨了
Look, there is no love lost between me and Charlie Baird.
虽然我不想承认 不过他的银行确实更强
Though it pains me to say it, his bank is stronger.
- 我就是这个意思 - 这是对未来更好的选择
- That's my point. - It's the right call for the future.
女士 你都不会有未来了
Ma'am, you are not going
如果援助查理的话
to have a future if you bail out Charlie.
好吧 再给我点时间
All right, I'm gonna need some more time.
至少杜鲁门下令扔原子弹的时候
At least when Truman made the decision to drop the bomb,
他没有正操着广岛的谁
he wasn't fucking anyone in Hiroshima.
只是我们不知道而已
That we know of.
你们好 我是乔纳·瑞安
Hello there. I'm Jonah Ryan.
支持乔纳 瑞安进国会
我在这里长大
And I grew up right here
就在这了不起的新罕布什尔州
in the awesome state of New Hampshire.
美国的花岗岩州[新罕布什尔州的别称]
The Granite State of the United States.
为了您的家庭和未来
For your family, for your future,
请投票支持瑞安成为国会议员
vote Ryan for Congress.
由乔纳 瑞安竞选委员会赞助
我是乔纳·瑞安 我赞同这条消息
My name is Jonah Ryan and I approve this message.
好了 现在你们都看过广告了
So, now you have all seen the ad
说说你们的想法吧[选举民调方法]
and we want to know what you think about it.
- 谁想说? - 我不喜欢那个人
- Anyone? - I didn't like the guy.
你不喜欢他?  好吧
You don't like him? Okay.
他砍的那块木柴 不会烧起来的
That wood he's chopping, it's not gonna burn right.
烧... 木头不会烧起来
To burn... the wood is not going to burn.
还有么?
What else?
对他身体来说脑袋太大了
His head is too big for his body.
不过有时候 又是身体太大脑袋太小了
But then sometimes his body is too big for his head.
- 他身材不好 - 身材不好?
- He's the wrong shape. - Shape is wrong?
有没有人想说一说这广告的优点?
Does anyone have anything positive to say about the ad?
- 我喜欢那个小孩 - 对
- I like the kid. - Yeah.
喜欢广告里的小孩 那个小男孩
Like the kid in the ad, the little boy.
不过不喜欢他在那个男人旁边
But I did not like that he was next to that guy.
简直想说 "赶紧跑啊 孩子"
I was like, "Run, kid."
惊喜啊 惊喜 看看谁来了
Oh, surprise, surprise. Look who's here.
你们这些笨蛋
Do you morons really not
真的不知道这是个双面镜么?
understand that this is a two-way mirror?
真的么? 被这技术吓到了?
Seriously? Are you shocked by that technology?
我他妈在白宫西翼工作
I work in the fucking West Wing,
你们这些乡下来的臭傻逼
you Pepperidge Farm ad motherfuckers.
- 操你妈 - 嘴巴放干净点
- Fuck you. - Watch your mouth.
穿着大妈牛仔裤的大屁股 你他妈坐下吧
Sit your fucking mom jeans ass down, dude.
你得学习控制一下自己的脾气
You've got to learn to control your fucking temper!
神啊
Lord.
我都没话说了
This is beyond language.
我清楚小组讨论的套路
I know the world of focus groups.
我觉得我们可能挑错候选人了
I think maybe we picked the wrong candidate.
凯瑟琳怎么做到又在那又在这的?
How is Catherine there and also here?
- 她不在这 女士 - 从什么时候?
- She's not here, ma'am. - Since when?
- 上周 - 我的天呐
- Last week. - Oh, my God.
更加操蛋的是
And then to put a fucking cherry on this shit sundae,
你们看到《政客》上那篇文章了吗?
did you guys see that article in "Politico"?
- 《梅耶的五大经济错误》? - 不是
- "Meyer's Five Biggest Economic Mistakes"? - No.
《为衰退代言:塞琳娜式下滑》?
"Recession Has a New Name: the Selina Slump"?
不是 盖瑞 机器拿来
No. Gary, you have the machine?
- 有 - 听听这个
- Yeah. - Listen to this.
"在进一步士气底下的形势下"...
"In a further sign of low morale"...
不对 你好好读
No, you've got to read it properly.
- 不对 不是这里 - 你要把它转一下
- Nope, that's not it. - You've got to spin it.
有了 为什么它一直转?
Here we go. Why does it keep doing the turning?
"一位位高权重的西翼员工最近被听到
"A high-level West Wing staffer was recently overheard
称总统为那个婊子"
calling the president the C word."
你们敢相信吗?
Can you believe this shit?
不可思议
That's crazy.
是吧 另外这玩意坏了
Yeah, this is broken, by the way.
女士 我觉得我们把注意力
Ma'am, I think that we need to resume our focus
恢复到乔纳的选举上
on relaunching Jonah's campaign.
我们要找个乔纳的耳边人
We need a Jonah whisperer,
但是要那种会吼他
except somebody who's gonna, like,
当面叫他傻子的那种人
yell in his face and call him stupid.
- 我们需要丹·伊根 - 丹拒绝了
- Oh, we need Dan Egan. - Dan turned us down.
但是还有一些面试
But I've got some interviews lined up.
- 我们会做出正确的决定的 -好吧 你们要现在做吗?
- We'll make the right choice. - Well, are you doing it?
还是你们只是坐在这对着我的沙发放屁
You're just sitting here farting into my couch.
走起 走起 走起
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
艾米 我需要跟你聊聊
Amy, I need to talk to you for a moment.
- 是的 女士 - 你去查查是谁骂我婊子的
- Yes, ma'am. - I want you to find out who called me a cunt.
- 女士... - 眼前投票的事 银行的事
- Ma'am... - Listen, with the votes and the banks,
- 我们堡垒里不能有叛徒 对吧? - 对...
- we can't have a traitor in our castle, right? - Yeah...
- 你得提个头来见我 - 是的 女士
- You need to bring me a head. - Yes, ma'am.
丹 你想一会一起去汉城韩国烧烤
Hey, Dan. You want to go to lunch later
吃午饭吗?
at Hansong Korean Barbecue?
我有团购券 周一过期
Come on, I've got a Groupon, expires Monday.
50美元尽享100美元的食物
50 bucks for $100 worth of food.
在安嫩代尔啊 迈克 [弗吉尼亚州东部]
It's in Annandale, Mike.
华盛顿的人不去哔了狗的安嫩代尔
No one from DC goes to fucking Annandale.
那40美金享受80美金的室内按摩 怎么样?
Hey, how about an $80 in-home massage for 40 bucks?
- 顺带爽一发? - 没有
- With release? - No.
- 那还有什么意思? - 嘿
- Then what's the point? - Hey,
你干嘛不接乔纳选举的工作?
why did you turn down the Jonah job?
- 拜托 - 天呐 丹 除非你弯腰被可乐瓶爆菊
- Come on. - Jesus, Dan, you wouldn't know the smart move
你没法做出正确的决定
if it bent you over and fucked you with a Coke bottle.
如果乔纳输了 没人会怪你
If Jonah loses, no one's gonna blame you.
- 如果他赢了 你就是个政治天才 - 我考虑一下
- If he wins, you're a political genius. - I'll think about it.
考虑快点  本正面试候选人呢
Think fast. Ben's interviewing candidates right now.
一点都不担心
Not worried.
闪开 闪开!
Move, move!
那个寡妇勇抗国旗的故事
The widow bravely carrying the flag narrative
只能吸引一周的新闻注意力
has traction for about a week.
之后就没了
After that, done.
嗨 本 我能...
Hey, Ben, can I...
丹 你认识凯蒂·卡罗索吗?
Dan, do you know Candi Caruso?
- 认识 - 不认识
- Yes. - No.
我能跟你说句话吗?
Can I speak to you for a second?
- 可以 抱歉 - 抱歉
- Yeah. Excuse me. - Sorry.
我很抱歉 凯蒂 我们的职位已经有人了
I'm sorry, Candi. The position's been filled.
感谢你前来
Thanks for coming in.
再次见到你很高兴
It's good seeing you again.
怎么了? 我有麻烦了吗?
What's this about? Am I in trouble?
不是 总统
No, no. The president
让我就一个特别的问题跟每个人谈谈
asked me to speak to everyone about a certain matter.
是关于我从厨房拿走的咖啡包吗?
Is this about the coffee pods I took from the kitchen?
- 我们吃了个早午餐然后我就拿了 - 不是
- We had a brunch and I took them. - No. No.
迈克 你知道是谁叫总统婊子了吗?
Mike, do you know who called the president a cunt?
不知道 我... 完全不知道
No, I-- I have no idea.
好吧 对不起 我做不来
Okay, I'm sorry. I can't do this.
她让我来领导这个傻逼的调查
She put me in charge of this whole stupid investigation
但是就是我做的 我骂她婊子的
and it was me. I called her a cunt.
是你?
You did?
我以为大家都知道是我
I thought everyone knew it was me.
我当时和丹在参议院的大楼里
I was in the Senate building with Dan
我确定有人听到了我
and I'm sure someone overheard me.
我在火车上的私密车厢里打电话时说的
I shouted it into my phone on the Acela Quiet Car.
周五 下午 3:09
距股票开市还有66小时
好吧
Okay.
我已经做出了决定
I've made my decision.
我们要援助查理的银行
We are going to bail out Charlie's bank.
我不在乎失多少选票
I don't care what hits we take.
从长远看这是为了国家好
It's for the good of the country in the long run.
- 干得漂亮 总统女士 - 对
- Bravo, Madam President. - Yeah.
- 女士 我能不能就... - 不能
- Ma'am, if I could just-- - Nope.
我不想听 好吗?
I don't want to hear it, okay?
这就是我的最终决定
That's my final solution.
我用了 《谁想成为百万富翁》里的梗
"Who Wants to be a Millionaire?"
明白了吗? 对
Do you get it? Yeah.
瑞安竞选总办公室
纳舒厄 新罕布什尔州
我绝对不能忘记
I can't ever forget
一切为了人民
it's about the people.
你有在拍吗?
Are you even getting any of this?
拍什么?
Getting what?
我正在全神贯注的凝视窗外啊
I was looking thoughtfully out the window.
明显的肯尼迪式深思啊
Some straight up JFK level shit.
我在给传真机拍一些幕后花絮
I was just getting some B-roll of the fax machine.
拜托!
Ah! Come on!
天呐
God.
你知道吗 你住的这个州烂死了
You know, the state that you live in sucks.
先生 作为你的交流总指挥
Sir, as your director of communications,
我需要告诉你我们刚刚收到了一封来自匆促乐团的信
I need to tell you that we just got a letter from the band Rush.
- 真的? - 他们说
- Really? - They said that
我们不能再用那首《工人》了
we can't use the song "Working Man" Anymore
因为他们讨厌你
because they find you odious.
我想放什么歌就放什么歌
You know what? I play what I want.
Zune出现之后版权就都是屎了
Copyright shit went out with the Zune.
哎呦 不好意思 你来这儿干嘛?
Whoa, I'm sorry. What are you doing here?
哟 乔纳 理查德
Hello, Jonah. Richard.
- 嗨 凯瑟琳 - 你跟我说话片子就毁了
- Hi, Catherine. - When you talk to me, you ruin the film.
看见你总是很舒畅啊
Always a pleasure.
我是你的新任竞选经理
I'm here to be your new campaign manager.
我天 你是过来求我找活儿干的吗?
Holy shit, are you here to beg me for a job?
作为通讯主任 我本该对这种事有所提防的
As director of communication, I should have been alerted to this.
哎呦 干嘛不坐下啊
Uh, why don't you have a seat
先说说你的工作经历 然后我们再详谈?
and tell me about your job history and we'll go from there?
乔纳 从现在开始
From now on, Jonah, you
他妈的闭上你那烂嘴 按我说的去做
will shut the fuck up and do exactly as I say.
要是你听了我的  而不是就靠你自个儿那
And if you listen to me instead of your only two brain cells
空荡荡的畸形脑袋瓜里
busy butt-fucking each other
天天忙着互相操对方菊花的俩脑细胞的话
somewhere in the vast expanses of your misshapen skull,
没准 乔纳 你没准还可能
then maybe, Jonah, you might have a chance
成为第一个赢得美国议员竞选的
at becoming the first mentally impaired Frankenstein's monster
脑残智障弗兰肯斯坦怪物
to ever win an American election.
捎带说一句 那些标语上
And by the way, your banner
你的名字看起来像 乔·H·赖安
makes it look like your name is Jon H. Ryan,
干得不错嘛 通讯部门
so great job, communications department.
- 这办公室是我的了 - 那是我的办公室
- I'm taking this office. - Wait, that's my office.
这我都录下了
I got that.
周五 下午 7:45
距股票开市还有62小时
这么大压力 你是怎么保持气色的
How do you look so good with all this stress?
整个人简直熠熠生辉
You're glowing.
实际上还看起来更年轻了 怎么保养的?
You actually look younger. What did you do?
天哪 他发现了
Oh, my God, he noticed.
- 啥? - 你知道的
- What? - Mmm.
我用了新的脸霜
Uh, I have a new facial moisturizer.
- 这样啊 - 还有新的香皂
- Oh. - And a new soap.
- 盖瑞 - 好 我就站这边儿
- Gary. - Yeah, I'll just stand over here.
- 实际上 我是想... - 那我还是出去吧
- Actually, I think - I'll just leave the room.
- 对快出去 - 好好好
- Yes. - Yeah.
赛琳娜 我想跟你说声抱歉
Listen, Selina, I want to apologize.
我知道我们的关系跟你的工作有冲突
I know that our relationship has compromised your job.
- 没错 - 但是你是总统
- Yeah. - But you're the president.
你的决定都是最好的
Whatever you decide is best.
你怎么决定也不会影响我们的关系
And it won't affect our relationship one way or another.
- 嗯 - 好了 不谈工作了
- Okay. - Now, enough shoptalk.
- 太好了 - 嗯
- Yeah, no kidding. - All right.
- 我们来聊点别的 - 行啊
- Let's talk about something else. - Yes.
- 你想不想直接来一发 - 想
- Do you want to just have sex? - Yeah.
- 成 - 那我们快点
- Yeah. - It's got to be quick, though.
九点半我就得撤了
I got wheels up at 9:30.
说的我都有点性奋
Ooh, that turns me on.
周六 上午 2:01
距股票开市还有55小时
- 您好 女士 - 艾米 到我办公室来一趟
- Hello, ma'am. -  Amy, come to my office.
- 现在? - 没错
- Right now? - Yeah.
好的
Of course.
提醒我
Set a reminder.
去预约冷冻卵子
Make an appointment to freeze eggs.
女士 你怎么样?
Ma'am, are you okay?
- 艾米 让你做的调查进行的怎么样了? - 挺顺利
- Amy, how's the investigation going? - Oh, uh, fine.
那个有人骂我婊子的调查
I mean, the investigation of me being called a cunt.
- 我知道您指的是哪个调查 - 那就行
- I knew which one you meant. - Yeah, good.
不过 我想
Well, it does occur to me
我们现在还有很多事要忙
that we've all got a lot on our plates right now.
- 嗯 - 所以 我觉得应该先把这调查放一放
- Yeah. - So I think we should push this investigation
等先把别的事搞完...
until after everything...
你去把那个杰瑞·杜肯
I want you to fire Gerry Duggan,
菲尔·内亚德 还有那个叫丽萨什么鬼的... 都给我开了
Phil Neary and what's her ass, Lisa...
- 哈奇? - 对就是她 把她踢出通讯部 听见了吗?
- Hatch? - Yeah, I want her out of the comms department, okay?
因为他们一开始就不应该让
Because they should not have let an article
有人骂我婊子这事被报到出去
about me being called a cunt get out in the first place, right?
- 那个 我没有资格... - 开了他们
- Well, I'm not the person who... - Fire them.
- 明白了 - 我是美国的第一任女性总统
- Okay. - I am the first female president
这次的事是种公开侮辱
of the United States and this is an affront.
是的女士
Yes, ma'am.
我告诉你 艾米
I'll tell you something, Amy.
有很多人都反对我当总统
A lot of people don't want me to be president.
原因你也知道  毕竟从根本上来讲
And you know why. Because fundamentally,
大家都不喜欢女人 不是么
people hate women, right?
我是说 为了把我赶下台 他们根本不会罢休的
I mean, they'll just stop at nothing to get me out of here.
谁都想抓我的把柄 但我绝对不会让他们得逞的
Everybody's trying to get me, but I'm not gonna let them.
你还好吗 女士?
You okay, ma'am?
你被骂过婊子吗?
Have you ever been called a cunt?
好多次
Many times.
现在我也算经历过了 一次
Well, now I have, too, apparently once.
周六 上午 9:08
距股票开市还有48小时
妈妈 我回来了
Hey, Mom, I'm back.
你原来不在这吗? 对 你去新罕布什尔了
You were gone? Oh, right, you were in New Hampshire.
- 盖瑞 现在方便吗? - 嗯啊
- Gary, is now a good time? - Mm-hmm.
- 什么? 我的时间又不归他管 - 嗯 是
- What? He's not in charge of me. - Mm-mmm.
- 我就是想问 你现在方便跟我说几句话吗? - 说吧
- I just wanted to know can we talk for a second? - Yeah.
我觉得 自从外婆去世后
I feel like since Mee-Maw died,
我有空来反省一些事了
I've had some time to reflect on things
你知道 就是为什么我跟杰森谈不来啊
and, you know, why things didn't work out between me and Jason.
- 这个  - 还有我跟学校里那个喜欢看我尿尿的人也分了
- Uh-huh. - Or the guy in college who wanted to watch me pee.
我跟那个声音高得奇怪的人也没有结果
Or the guy with the weirdly high voice.
不 是有两个人声音都挺尖的
No, there were two guys with weirdly high voices.
- 对 是两个 - 你记得吗?
- Yeah, there were two. - Do you remember?
- 我尝试着...  - 总统女士
- I've been trying... -  Madam President.
怎么了? 凯瑟琳 我现在有事要处理
Yeah? I have to deal with whatever this is, okay, Catherine?
待会儿再聊
So we can talk later.
- 我什么都不想听 - 女士
- Guys, I don't want to hear it. - Ma'am.
- 女士 - 不 先生们 你知道我不会重新考虑这事儿了
- Ma'am. - No, guys, you know I'm not gonna rethink it.
- 我已经做了决定 - 总统女士!
- I've made the decision. - Madam President!
如果你还想保住这头衔的话!
That is if you'd like for that to remain your title!
天哪 怎么啦?
Wow. What?
事情比我们想的还糟
It's worse than we thought.
我算了下 援助你性伴侣的银行
I ran the numbers. Approval rating for bailing out
这件事的支持率只有... 4.3%
your sexual partner's financial establishment... 4.3%.
光明节在麦加的民调都比这个高[光明节为犹太节日 麦加为伊斯兰圣地]
Hanukah polls higher in Mecca.
但经济上讲确实该援助这个银行对吧?
But it's the right bank to bail out, right?
是的 女士 可没有人懂经济
That's right, ma'am, but nobody understands the economy.
- 完全真没人懂 - 也不能说完全
- Literally nobody. - Not literally.
我们就这样会在
And then I think we lose
国会输掉三、四个州的
three or four states in Congress just like that.
如果硬要你们在屌和蛋之间选一个
What would you guys do if you
你们会怎么做?
had to choose between your cock and your balls?
我可以都不要 现阶段
I could lose them both. I mean,
对我来说它们都只是装饰物
at this stage they're purely decorative.
同志们 有谁等会儿想去吃韩国汉城烤肉的吗?
Guys, you want to go out later for some Hansong Korean Barbecue?
韩国烤肉就是山寨一点都不正宗
Korean barbecue is a travesty and a far cry from authentic.
- 加一 - 苏?
- I'm his plus one. - Sue?
刚说的是韩语的"我恨你"
That's Korean for "I hate you."
马乔里?
Marjorie?
这是她名字吧?
That is her name, right?
周六 上午 9:42
距股票开市还有47小时
各位 很抱歉这么做
Sorry to do this, everyone.
但我已经慎重思考过了
But I've done some deep soul diving
我们要援助鲍尔斯丁-博尔翰
and we are going to bail out Paulsten Berheim.
- 擦 - 想办法吧
- Oh, fuck. - Make that happen.
谢谢他妈不存在的上帝
Thank nonexistent Jesus.
乔纳 瑞安竞选宣传站
新罕布什尔州
雪莉
不行 我不想戴眼镜
No, I don't know. I don't want to wear the glasses.
这是你新形象的一部分
They're part of your relaunch.
让你看起来聪明多了 你个傻逼
They make you look half smart, you fucking goon.
你知道我们那个年代怎么称呼你这种人吗?
You know what we call people like you back in my day?
智障
Retards.
汤姆·裴迪[歌手]说不能再放他的《永不退缩》了
Tom Petty says we can't use "Won't Back Down" Anymore.
好 操他妈的要是他以为我会退缩的话
Okay, well, fuck him if he thinks I'm gonna back down.
这就是整首歌的全部意义
That's, like, the whole point of the song.
不过我们得到加里·格利特的同意了
We got the okay from Gary Glitter,
不过他还因为强奸儿童在监狱待着呢 所以这个不太好吧
but he's in jail for child rape, so maybe not the first choice.
这样 听我说
Okay, all right, now listen to me.
走出去 扭转乾坤 好吗?
Go out there, turn this thing around, all right?
那个寡妇还领先你30个点
The widow's beating you by 30 points.
天啊 人家还只是一个退休的二年级老师
She's a retired second grade teacher, for Christ's sake.
是啊 变态死了 还布置那么多作业
Yeah, who sucks and gives too much homework.
- 她是你的二年级老师? - 是啊
- She's your second grade teacher? - Yeah.
乔纳·瑞安 幸会 谢谢你的到来 先生
Jonah Ryan, pleasure to meet you. Thanks for coming out, sir.
乔纳·瑞安 在竞选国会议员 很高兴见到你
Jonah Ryan, running for Congress. Pleasure to meet you.
给我和这位老先生的胡子留个影
Get a picture of me and this guy's mustache.
乔纳·瑞安 女士 我的早饭在那后面
Jonah Ryan. Ma'am, I have some breakfast back there.
你真该试试这个牛肉马铃薯饼
You should really try the corned beef hash.
比监狱里方法的任何菜
It's so much more agreeable than anything
都要美味多了
that gets dished out in prison.
比尔 我以为你还在...
Bill. I thought you were in the...
监狱? 我的律师帮我上诉否决了
The slammer? My lawyer got it thrown out on appeal.
奥布莱恩聘请我做寡妇谢尔曼的新任竞选经理
O'Brien hired me to be the Widow Sherman's new campaign manager.
- 你别逗我啊 - 没有 丹
- You're kidding me. - No, Dan.
在监狱能学到的一件事就是永远别开玩笑
One thing you learn in prison is not to make jokes.
我对果糖过敏 你个傻子
I am fructose intolerant, you nitwit.
我现在看到的傻逼局面是专利性的伊根杰作吧
I assume what I'm seeing is the patented Egan touch.
朋友 竞选游说时再会了
I'll see you on the campaign trail, amigo.
告诉总统别见怪
Tell the president no hard feelings.
噢 等等 没错
Oh, wait, that's right.
我倒是很受伤 都快被此吞噬完了
I do have hard feelings. I'm consumed by them.
...我们不是在这种情况下
...we're not in this situation.
结束了 丹 我们走吧
This is done. Dan, we got to go.
- 是 - 丹
- Yeah. Yes. - Dan.
周六 上午 11:06
距股票开市还有46小时
凯瑟琳
Oh, Catherine.
亲爱的 你不是想跟我私下谈谈吗
Honey, you wanted to talk to me privately before.
- 现在就可以 - 真的?
- Now is a perfect time. - Really?
嗯 你那个尖嗓子男朋友怎么了?
Mm-hmm. Now, what happened to the boyfriend with the high voice?
他不能去卫生间了?
He couldn't go to the bathroom?
不止是我情感上的事
What it was more about was just my relationships
- 还有我在研究的一种常见形式... - 女士
- and examining a sort of common pattern... - Ma'am.
- 怎么? - 我想... 嗨 凯瑟琳
- Yeah? - I wondered... hey, Catherine.
我想我们能谈一下吗?
I wondered if you and I could just have a moment together?
- 单独 - 当然
- Privately. - Definitely.
我等会儿再跟你谈
I'm gonna talk to you later.
汤姆 我不觉得...
Tom, I don't think...
你跟着干嘛?
where are you going?
女士 大家都知道你是一个
Ma'am, you are known to be
- 非常聪明的政治家 - 我知道
- a very smart political operator. - I know.
下午好 又见面啦
Good afternoon. Hello again.
经过再三考虑 我们准备援助
On second thought, we are now going to bail out
查理和韦瑞特银行 谢谢
Charlie and Wheelright. Thank you.
不 这样吧
No. You know what?
经过再四考虑 我们还是继续采用之前的计划吧
On third thought, let's just stick with the plan before.
还是援助鲍尔斯丁
We're going to bail out Paulsten.
就这样
Yeah. Yeah.
谁赌的12点50出决定来着?
So, who had 12:50 P.M.?
罗德曼折扣食品药品商店
你原来吃饭的啊
Huh, you eat.
不然每天紧张地拉什么屎呢
I suppose you need something to nervously shit out.
里昂 每次看到你这张在Tinder[交友app]
Hello, Leon. It's always good to see
最被人左划的脸还是不错的[左划表示没好感]
the most left-swiped face on Tinder.
忙啊 通讯部今天开除了三个人
Busy day. Three people fired from the communications office.
人事变更率很高的部门嘛
High turnover department.
或许是个惊慌失措的大批量解雇呢
Or is a panicky mass firing
因为有人在《政客》上称总统为婊子[又译阴道]?
because someone called POTUS a cunt in "Politico"?
啊 不小心揭露了逼门事件[引用水门事件]
Ah, I just blew the lid off of Cuntgate.
- 这还算不上个门事件 - 不 当然算了
- It's not a gate. - No, it's very much a gate.
- 不是真的 - 你该小心点 艾米
- Untrue. - You should watch out, Amy.
你不会想成为逼门事件的代言人的
You don't want to be the face of Cuntgate.
尽管你的脸非常适合
Although you do have the perfect face for it.
周六 下午 8:15
距股票开市还有37小时
所以已经传到保险公司了?
So it spread to the insurance companies?
- 至少已经三个人了 - 我的天啊
- At least three of them. - Jesus Christ.
又来
Oh, come on.
晚上好 我又来了
Good evening. It is me again.
我刚跟迈克谈了一下
Um, yeah, so I was just talking to Mike
我决定要援助韦瑞特
and I definitely want to bail out Wheelright.
这是个更聪明的选择
That's a smart play.
迈克! 你这臭傻逼
Mike! You fucking jagoff.
关于咖啡包的事儿真的很抱歉 我发誓我只是...
Is this about the coffee pods? I swear I was gonna put...
不 是你告诉总统要援助查理的银行
No, you told the president to bail out Charlie's bank.
我没说银行的事啊
No, I didn't say anything about banks.
我就跟她说了温蒂付清了
I was talking to her about how Wendy paid off
我的助学贷款 我因此多爱她
my student loans and how I love her for it.
你还没还完学生贷款啊? 你都多大了?
You still have student loans? How old are you?
我不太会理财嘛
I'm not good with money.
市政厅会议
利奇菲尔德 新罕布什尔州
那个寡妇有10分钟 你也有10分钟时间
Now, the widow's gonna get 10 minutes, then you get 10 minutes.
嗨 我叫乔纳·瑞安 很高兴站在这里 真是莫大的荣幸
Hi, I'm Jonah Ryan. So happy to be here. What a great cause.
- 竞选演讲套路嘛 - 我的信条是多倾听多行动
- Stump speech. - I'm listening and I'm a doer.
开头来一个关于当地大咖的笑话 比如现场的布鲁克市长
It's good to start with a joke about a local bigwig
可能效果会很好
like Mayor Brock is here tonight.
比如他得癌症那会 他的医生不得不切除
I guess when he had cancer, the doctors removed
他操自己家保姆的能力
his ability to stop doing his kid's babysitter.
太残酷了吧
Seems kind of harsh.
我了解新罕布什尔的习俗 信我 这是个大笑点
I know New Hampshire. Trust me, big laugh.
先生 一些我们都没用过的乐队
Also, sir, some bands we haven't used
发来一些警告函
have sent some preemptive cease-and-desist orders.
斯汀 布鲁斯·斯普林斯汀...
Sting, Bruce Springsteen...
发来两封 还有恩雅
sent two letters, actually-- and Enya.
恩雅?
Enya?
给她发一封警告函吧
Send her a fucking cease-and-desist letter.
- 你好 乔纳 - 早上好 谢尔曼女士
- Hello, Jonah. - Good morning, Mrs. Sherman.
我还记得你给你妈妈的那幅
I still remember that lovely macaroni portrait
用空心面拼的肖像画
you made of your mother.
我可不记得什么空心面画像 谢尔曼女士
I don't recall that macaroni portrait, Mrs. Sherman.
- 有请... - 不好意思 女士 该你出场了
- Please welcome... - Excuse me, ma'am. You're on.
...我们第一位演讲者 朱迪·谢尔曼女士
...our first speaker, Mrs. Judy Sherman.
谢谢
Thank you.
你听见她用空心粉画像嘲讽我了吗?
Did you hear that dig about the macaroni portrait?
你他妈能相信吗?
Can you fucking believe that?
我们现在有大危机了
Hey, we're on a code black.
总统现在什么疯言疯语都听信 快来
POTUS is on an opinion shopping spree. Come on.
你慢点 我最近在吃可迈丁
Hey, slow down. I'm on Coumadin.
苏 我们要见总统
Sue, we need to see the president.
先生们 你们先擦擦汗 耐心等待一下吧
Gentlemen, you'll have to towel off and wait.
- 她在跟别人谈话呢 - 谁?
- She's in with someone. - Who?
和谁
Whom.
别犹豫 就查理了
Come on, Charlie, 100%.
- 好啊 - 就这么说定了
- 100%. - All right, great.
不过话说回来 援助你的男朋友
Now, on the other hand, bailing out your boyfriend,
会不会结束你的职业生涯啊?
I mean, that could be career-ending, right?
对吼
Yeah, right.
但有把枪抵在你的头上...
But, I mean, if you had a gun to your head...
或许枪里没有子弹啊
Oh, maybe the gun doesn't have any bullets.
感谢你的来访
Well, thank you so much for coming.
我的荣幸 先生们
It was my pleasure. Oh, gentlemen.
她真是屁用没有
Well, that was completely useless.
女士 我们得做出最后决定了
Ma'am, we need a final decision right now,
即使它是错误决定
even if it's the wrong one.
我就再需要一丢丢时间
I just need a little bit more time.
如果明天早上我们还拿不出执行方案
If we don't put a plan into action tomorrow morning,
周一我们就变成希腊了
then by Monday we will be Greece.
国家希腊 不是音乐剧希腊
The country, not the musical.
好 我的最终决定是
All right, here's my final decision.
明天早上你们会收到一个最终决定
You will have a final decision by tomorrow morning.
做好两手准备
Have both plans ready to go.
现在我要跟以色列总理电话会谈
Now, I need to get on the phone with the Israeli prime minister
接着还有法国总统 好吗?
and then the president of France, okay?
说不定他们能给我点建议呢
They may give me some insight into this.
女士 与其这样 不如听听我的主意
Ma'am, instead of that, I got an idea.
你现在什么都别想 该咋玩儿咋玩儿
You can clear your head out and have a little fun at the same time.
- 说啥? - 是的 我会打电话给乔纳和丹
- What? - Yeah, I'll call Jonah and Dan
然后你就把他们骂得来找不着北
and you can tear them a six-pack of new assholes.
- 听起来很不错呢 - 是的
- Oh, that does sound like fun. Okay. - Yeah.
但是当和你一起度过了47年的丈夫
But when your husband of 47 years
在病榻前问你时...
asks you on his deathbed...
丹 现在总统要跟你通电话
Dan, you're on with the president.
丹 我真特么不敢相信
Dan, I cannot fucking believe
你把工作整得一团糟
how terrible you are at your job.
你现在为了调高税收和外阴切开手术
What, are you running on a platform
而奔波演讲吗?
of higher taxes and episiotomies?
女士 我们需要一点时间
Ma'am, we just-- we need a little time.
让世界上最高那坨垃圾接电话
Put that world's tallest pile of garbage on the phone right now.
总统电话
It's the president.
妈的...
Fuck...
- 你好 女士 - 你好啊 驼背大哥
- Hello, ma'am. - Hey, hunchback.
我不知道你每天不忙着赢 反而在瞎逼忙什么
I don't know what you've been doing instead of trying to win,
但是肯定跟屁股和菊花有关系
but I'm gonna guess that it has the word anal in it.
你现在学学怎么控制你那舔屌的脾气
Now, you learn to control your cocksucking temper,
否则我就会亲自现身
otherwise I'm gonna come up there myself
然后揍得你满地找牙
and I'm gonna shoot you in your fucking mouth.
- 她挂电话了 - 操她妈的
- She hung up. - Fuck her.
塞琳娜·梅耶就是个平庸之辈
You know, Selina Meyer is a second-rate mediocrity
她的唯一成就就是一手搞垮了经济
whose only achievement is single-handedly tanking the economy.
怎么我们成了互相舔菊的傻屌了?
But somehow we're the losers doing anal with each other?
她的总统生涯就是一个接一个的耻辱
Her entire presidency has been one disgrace after another.
- 她从来都不尊重我 - 我他妈的工作还做得不好吗?
- She has never respected me. - And I'm bad at my fucking job?
- 妈蛋！ - 都他妈是狗屁
- Fuck! - You know what? That's bullshit.
- 你做得很好 - 拉倒吧
- You're doing a good job. - Oh, fuck off.
说真的 眼镜啊什么都 高招啊
No, this glasses shit, that was dope.
越看越顺眼 真是个好主意
These look great. That was a great idea.
去你的 真讨厌
Go fuck yourself.
我保证我不会让任何人
And I promise I won't let anyone get away
挥霍你辛辛苦苦的血汗钱
with wasting your hard-earned money.
谢谢你们
Thank you. Thank you so much.
谢谢
Thank you.
你给我上去
I want you to go out there
好好地震慑一下新罕布什尔
and I want you to kick some New Hampshire ass.
花岗岩之州 你们好吗
Yo, Granite State. Hey, how you feeling?
布洛克市长今天不在啊[乔纳叫错名字]
I see that Mayor Block isn't here tonight.
是不是因为他不到保姆了[笑话讲错]
Guess he couldn't get a babysitter.
或者其实找到了?
Or could he?
你个怂货 滚回华盛顿把
You suck! Go back to Washington.
我安排了一些激进分子
I took the liberty of arranging some hecklers.
- 免费的哟 - 我是来自华盛顿
- No charge. - But, yes, I was in Washington.
而且我的职位非常高 职责很重大
And I worked a very high-level, important job.
你是塞琳娜·梅耶搞垮这个国家的帮凶
You helped Selina Meyer screw up this country.
把国家搞垮是塞琳娜自己做的好吗
I think she did a fine job screwing up the country all by herself.
不 我是认真的
No, I'm serious.
这比看我自己孩子出生
This is so much more
刺激多了
beautiful to watch than the birth of my child.
对 她一个人就完全搞垮了经济
Right, she single-handedly destroyed the economy,
但是她根本不在乎
but she doesn't care because she's too busy
因为她正忙着跟大款男朋友抱抱呢
cuddling up to her billionaire boyfriend.
我不知道你们怎样
And I don't know about you,
反正我的男朋友可不是大款
but my boyfriend's not a billionaire.
她的整个总统任期就是从一个耻辱走向另一个耻辱
Her whole presidency has been one disgrace after another
不知道你是不是受够了
and I don't know if you're sick of it,
- 反正我是受够了 - 没错
- but I am definitely sick of it... - Yes.
我可不打算再继续逆来顺受下去了
...and I'm not just gonna sit here and take it anymore.
怎么回事
What the fuck?
我是乔纳·瑞安
My name is Jonah Ryan
我要做你们的议员
and I want to be your congressman.
我不会退缩 谢谢
And I won't back down. Thank you.
谢谢你们 花岗岩之州
Thank you very much, Granite State.
感觉到我的热情了吗 谢谢
You feeling me? Thank you.
谢谢
Thank you.
周日 上午 9:07
距股票开市还有24小时
- 迈克 迈克 - 韦恩
- Mike! Mike! - Wayne.
什么时候才能知道哪家银行能得到救助资金?
When will we hear which banks are gonna get bailout money?
只有你管那叫救济金 韦恩
No one is using the term bailout money except for you, Wayne.
相关细节会在过后透露
The details for the plan will be revealed later today.
里昂
Leon.
你能证实对通讯部
Can you confirm the allegation of the firing
那三个人的
of three people from the comms
下周二见门的解雇吗[cuntgate逼门事件]
office is tied to See-you-next-Tuesday-gate?
这种这粗俗的语言
That sort of coarse language
简直玷污了这间屋子
is far beneath the dignity of this room.
- 而且那玩意不算个门 - 就是个门
- And also it's not a gate. - Oh, it's a gate.
- 就不是  - 就是
- No, it is not a gate. - It's very much a gate.
你猜怎么着 我要让《纽约时报》的
You know what? We're gonna elevate the conversation,
朋友继续提问了
go to my friend here at "The New York Times."
迈克 在《政客》的侧边栏上
Mike, the "Politico" Sidebar suggested
登出了一则新闻 说一位员工用最恶毒的语言
that there was one staffer who called the president
辱骂了总统女士
the worst thing you can call a woman.
- 为什么有三个人被解雇了 - 好了 提问结束
- Why were three people fired? - Okay, that about wraps it up.
谢谢大家 提问结束了
Thank you all. No further questions.
祝晚上愉快
Enjoy your evening.
本 整间屋子都在问逼门的事情
Ben, this is real. The whole room was sniffing around Cuntgate.
- 那不算一个门 - 废话!
- It's not a gate, Mike. - No kidding!
这真的不算一个门 我同意 我就说嘛
It isn't a gate. I agree. I said that.
她真的精神错乱了
She's becoming seriously unhinged.
她正在向尼克松的方向发展
She has gone full metal Nixon.
你觉得是谁说的
Who do you think said it?
好吧 我们说的 我和迈克
Well, we did. Me and Mike.
- 我的天 我以为是我 - 不是吧
- Oh, my God. I thought it was me. - No way.
不 我确定我在记者面前
No, I'm pretty sure I called
叫她婊子并且说漏了嘴
her a cunt to the reporter who broke the story.
艾米 很有可能你的调查
Amy, it's probable that your investigation
已经查出了我就是骂她婊子的那个人
has already determined that I was the one that called her a cunt.
我希望我对组织所起的作用
I'm hoping that my utility to the organization
能够让你保护我
gives you reason to protect me on this.
再加上我们的友谊之船
Also our friendship.
我说 本
Hey, Ben?
盖瑞
Gary.
是我 我骂了总统那个C开头的词
It was me. I called the president the C word.
- 不会吧 - 真的吗
- No, you didn't. - Really?
她没涂防晒霜我太生气了
I was so mad about her not wearing sunscreen,
我知道很蠢 但我说了
which is stupid, and I was like,
这个老丑婆
"What an old crone."
你说她什么
A what?
老女人 艾米
An old crone, Amy.
盖瑞 C开头的词是指婊子
Gary, C is for cunt.
什么?
What?
我们都骂了她婊子
We all called her a cunt.
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
你们怎么回事
What is wrong with you people?
总统女士 欢迎
Oh, Madam President. Welcome.
我决定了
I've made my final decision.
我要援助查理
I'm gonna bail out Charlie.
总统女士 您要三思啊
Madam President, you really don't have to make that decision yet.
我的意思是 你还有时间
I mean, you got a little bit more time.
我不需要时间
I don't need more time.
这对我国的经济来说是最好的
It's best for our country's economy.
就这么定了
That's the end of it.
你去跟财政财政部说
So you're gonna go talk to Treasury,
我去告诉汤姆 就这样 好吗
I'm gonna go tell Tom. Done. Okay?
- 听见了吗? - 是的 女士
- Right? - Yes, ma'am.
嘿 女士 我知道你跟查理在一起是对的
Hey, ma'am, I know you made the right choice with Charlie
因为当你找到你爱的人
because when you have found someone you love,
每次他跟你说话的时候你都会觉得很特别
who makes you feel special every time he talks to you
而且你光是想到他就会觉得很幸福
and you can be happy just thinking about him, you know--
我是说 那比别的什么都重要 是吧
I mean, that's more important than anything, you know?
对
Yeah.
- 早上好 - 早上好 总统女士
- Good morning. - Morning, ma'am.
总统女士
Madam President.
你怎么来了?
What brings you here?
我们开始吧
Let's do this.
周日 上午 10:30
宣传拍照 总统的圣诞购物
总统夫人 你要给贝尔德先生买什么礼物?
Madam President, what will you be buying for Mr. Baird?
我可不想毁了查理
I don't want to spoil Charlie's surprise
在树下的惊喜...[圣诞礼物都放在圣诞树下]
under the tree...
我准备买一本
but I'm going to be purchasing a book of poetry
我最喜欢的黑人诗人万达·科尔曼所著的诗集
by one of my favorite African-American poets, Wanda Coleman.
我还看中了一本
And I've got my eye on a graphic novel
以一位强健的亚洲女性为主角的漫画小说
with a very strong female Asian protagonist.
那么 圣诞快...
So, merry Chris...
祝每个人都节日快乐 是吗?
happy holidays to everybody, right?
- 是啊 - 让我们去购物吧 谢谢
- Right. - And let's go shopping. Thank you.
请别给我买本书当圣诞礼物
Please don't get me a book for Christmas.
我已经有一本了
I already have a book.
是汤姆·詹姆斯 我应该接的
It's Tom James. I should actually take this.
不 那不应该在现在打来的
No, no, that wasn't supposed to come now.
女士 凯瑟琳一直在打电话给你
Hey, ma'am. Catherine keeps calling.
- 你想接吗? - 什么?
- Do you want to take it? - Uh, what?
- 就让它响着吧 - 好的
- No, just let it ring. - Okay.
我不懂她为什么一直要打给我
I don't know why she keeps calling.
你准备什么时候告诉我的?
When were you gonna let me know?
- 我... - 我要破产了
- I... - I'm Chapter 11.
简第斯在购入我的资产
Janders is buying my assets.
我现在就尼玛是在院子里贱卖货物的大老板
I'm CEO of a fucking yard sale.
查理 你知道吗?
Hey, Charlie, you know what?
你他妈怎么能这么对我?
How could you fucking do this to me?
- 你什么意思? - 《政客》说得对
- What do you mean? - "Politico" Was right about you.
- 不 查理 - 你说过不会影响...
- No, Charlie... - Hey, you said it wouldn't affect...
我知道你眼睛整过了
I know you had an eye job.
周一 下午 5:32
道琼斯指数
女士 你选了正确的银行
You made the right call on the banks, ma'am.
你可以为此感谢《当哈利遇上莎莉》
Well, you can thank "When Gary Met Sally" for that one.
他对我说了些蠢话
He gave me some sappy speech
让我知道我有多么白痴
and made me realize what an idiot I was being.
女士 还有更好的消息 乔納支持率大涨
In further good news, ma'am, Jonah had a huge polling bump
因为他突然改变策略攻击你
since he hit on the strategy of attacking you.
什么? 他在攻击我?
What? He's attacking me?
是的 选民们爱死啦
Yeah, and the voters, they love it.
- 那很棒吗? - 真的很棒
- Is that good? - It's really good.
苏 查理打电话来了吗?
Oh. Hey, Sue, did Charlie call?
- 女士 没有 - 好吧
- No, ma'am. - Okay.
妈妈
Mom, there's something that
有些话我必须得和你说
I really need to find a way to say to you.
凯瑟琳 我现在忙得跟翔一样...
Catherine, I'm in the middle of a shitstorm like...
请务必给我时间 我整整三天都想找你
Please, I've been trying to talk to
我必须告诉你一件事
you for three days and I need to tell you something.
什么事 凯瑟琳? 什么事那么紧迫?
What is it, Catherine? What is it that is so pressing?
我在和某人约会 我知道这很尴尬
I've met someone and I know that this is awkward
因为你和他们一起工作
because you work with them,
但我们相爱了
but we're in love.
是谁?
Who?
我和马乔里
Me and Marjorie.
谁?
Who?
是我 女士
Me, ma'am.
什么?
What?
现在你知道我为什么总是傻里傻气 咯咯乱笑了吧
Now you know why I've been acting all silly and giggly.
- 好啊 - 好
- Hi. - Hi.
我们觉得你应该已经猜到了吧
We figured you guessed already.
我是说 太明显了
I mean, I know it's so obvious.
并没有 并没有
Didn't guess. Didn't guess.
- 我... - 太不可思议了
- I... - Amazing.
真的太... 不可思议了
It's... amazing.
我和帕克主管说了
I've told Director Parker
我会立即辞职的
I'll be resigning from your detail immediately.
好的 姑娘们
Okay, I'm just gonna need
我只是需要点时间消化一下
a little moment to process all of this, girls.
当然了 女士
Of course, ma'am.
但我真心替你们感到高兴
But I'm happy for you.
- 谢谢 夫人 - 谢谢 妈妈
- Thank you, ma'am. - Thanks, Mom.
- 我爱你 - 谢谢
- I love you. - Thank you.
什么...
What...
真希望我妈还活着
I wish Mother were alive.
这事儿绝对会逼死她的
Cause this definitely would have killed her.
你知道她是什么样的人
You know how she was.
- 夫人 现在方便说话吗? - 当然了
- Ma'am, is this a good time? - You bet.
我们还在继续严密的调查
The investigation continues at a rigorous pace.
那么谁说我是婊子的?
So who called me a cunt?
- 每个人都这么说吗? - 差不多吧
- Was it everybody? - Pretty much, yeah.
你可以出去了
You can go.
- 女士 - 不行
- Ma'am... - No.
好吧
Okay.
你好 之前电话预订了打包一百美元的食物带走
Hi, called ahead for $100 worth of food to go.
用麦克林托克的名字订的
Under McLintock.
我要用团购券
And I'll be using a Groupon.
- 本店不收团购券 - 你们必须得收
- We don't take Groupon. - You have to take Groupon.
我花钱买的这个团购券 先生
I already paid money for this Groupon, sir.
不收团购券 总共184.12美元
No Groupon. Total is $184.12.
我和电话里的那个人说订一百美元食物的
Whoa, I told the guy on the phone $100 worth of food.
这八十九美元是哪来的?
Where's this $89 coming from?
那就得问你啦 先生
That's your problem, sir.
操 我的天哪 我的天哪
Shit! Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
别啊 别啊
No, no, no, no.
我幸福得住不住笑
I can't stop smiling.